ALI MATHOFANI

BACKEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Having worked over 2.5 years in the tech and web division. I've grown and learned a great deal, and as I really began to focus on what I truly love and enjoy, I developed an enormous passion for coding and web development even networking. I am passionate about building websites, apps, server and the challenges that programming requires.

CONTACT DETAILS

Gunung Anyar Lor II/50, 60294 Surabaya, Jawa Timur Email: alimathofani@gmail.com Portfolio:: alimathofani.com LinkedIn: @alimathofani Skype: live:alimathofani Github: alimathofani

SKILLS

Laravel/Lumen/CakePHP, PHP, CSS, HTML, JQuery, Javascript, GIT, Linux, Nginx, MySQL, PostgreSQL, AWS, Node / Express, REST API, Docker.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Universitas Negeri Surabaya

D3 Manajemen Informatika May 2012 - Nov 2015

Learn all networking and programming and slightly playing the games

SMKN 11 Surabaya

Multimedia 2009 - 2012

Learn all networking and programming

LANGUAGES

Indonesia: 5/5 English: 4/5

PERSONAL PROJECTS

showcase.alimathofani.com/forecasting - Forecasting Projects

datindonesia.com (2017)

- Web Profile, Email Blast, Email Server risetpjokindonesia.com (2016)

- Reporting Academy Researches

WORK HISTORY

Back-end Developer

Mospaze.com | Sep 2018 - Sep 2019

Worked as a Laravel Developer, build and maintain web applications. Creating new features gradually with the agile scrum method. Writing code by implement design patterns as scalable code and adhere to best practices.

Skill: Laravel, JQuery, SASS/SCSS, Javascript, AWS SNS, Web Whatsapp Notification, GIT Flow, Testing, Optimized Query, Google API

Web Developer

Wave Game | Oct 2017 - Sep 2018

Competing for the best, fastest, and reliable creating the website. Worked as requested by the game master to create a websites or new features with a tight deadline. The bug always there and try to fix them including reducing query process for report finance page. There are also several projects integrate with Rest API and payment gateway. Not forget to documentation or report.

Portfolio:

- newran.wavegame.net/home # build from scratch
- soulark.wavegame.net/home # build from scratch
- mforex.wavepoint.co.id # Connecting API, build from scratch
- etc

Skill: CakePHP (1,2,3), Laravel, Jquery, MySQL, PostgreSQL, GIT. CSS. HTML. Rest API. OAUTH2. Trello

IT Support

PT Sukses Mekar Abadi | April 2016 - Mei 2017

First time job, worked with hardware, cable, and electricity. Learn the network to connect between 11 branches in Eastern Indonesia. The result like CCTV, Digital System Core, Private Email, Remote Desktop, Internet, And Server. My scope is also procurement for IT Infrastructure and some hardware with slightly bid on a purchase.

Skill: CCTV, MikroTik, Windows Server, Active Directory, Desktop Sharing, Remote Desktop, Management Bandwith, Web Server, MySQL